Scott Hardy

ScottHardy4555@outlook.com ❖ (314) 825-7168 ❖ St Louis, MO

GitHub: https://github.com/ScottHardy4555
Portfolio: https://scotthardy4555.github.io/index.html

SUMMARY

Self-driven programmer with four years of programming experience. Proficient in programming in languages such as C#, JavaScript, HTML5, and CSS. Excellent interpersonal skills and experience tutoring individuals in computer science and mathematics. Hard worker with an emphasis on teamwork, self-improvement, and attention to detail.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Skills: C#, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, GIT, React.JS, SQL, MS Office, OOP, mathematics, computer science.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mathnasium Jun. 2023 – Present

Instructor St Louis, MO

- Develop and communicate an understanding of mathematics and critical thinking skills.
- Assist in test preparation for students.
- Provide effective studying habits and strategies.
- Track progress of individual students and identify methods to improve lesson retention.

Ranken Technical College

Nov. 2022 - Present

Tutor

St Louis, MO

- Help classmates in deepening their understanding of the curriculum.
- Began weekly discussions to provide an open forum for classmates.
- Get to know each student individually and understand their specific problems.
 - O Worked with up to 9 students at a given time.
- Help classmates catch up with assignments and understand the requirements.

The UPS Store August 2022 – March 2023

Retail Associate

Chesterfield, MO

- Responsible for solo operation of the store from open to close.
- Provide mailing and shipping services to customers.
- Communicate shipping procedures and requirements.
- Provide solutions to unique customer inquiries and requests.

EDUCATION

Ranken Technical College

August 2022 – May 2024

St. Louis, MO

- AS, Application and Web Development

 Fall semester GPA of 3.8
- Aided classmates by providing tutoring services for classmates.
- Started a weekly extracurricular study group that discussed topics beyond the curriculum.

Parkway West High

High School Diploma

• Served as senior programmer for high school robotics team.

Recommendations available upon request